fashionnova.com 2019-09-26

# Privacy Policy – Fashion Nova

**Fashion Nova Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: May 25, 2018

Fashion Nova, Inc., (“Fashion Nova,” “We,” “Us,” “Our”) is committed to protecting both the personal as well as business information you share and/or store with us. By using this website, you consent to this Privacy Policy, which applies to transactions and activities and data gathered through the Fashion Nova Website and interaction you may have with its related Social Media accounts. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may revise it without notice.  
  
 **The Controller**

The controller for the collection, processing and use of your personal data for www.fashionnova.com ("website" or "our site") is:   
  
Fashion Nova

Address: 2801 East 46th Vernon, CA 90058

Email: info@ fashionnova.com

**Use by Fashion Nova**

As a visitor not registered on FashionNova: 

By visiting a website, the files are sent from your browser to the site to allow the transfer of information.   
  
As a FashionNova member: 

We protect direct access to your member account with a password. Your personal information will be collected on a secure server using a coding system called Secure Socket Layer (SSL). The collected data is kept safe and we will do our best to provide a high level of security. We handle your personal and account information carefully - and do not share it with anyone else. Remember to always disconnect completely when using public access computers. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account.

**The Collection, Processing, and use of Personal Data**

Personal data is all information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person, such as name, date of birth, bank details. Generally, we collect information that may personally identify you when you voluntarily:

register an account on this Website,  
place an order,  
enter a contest or sweepstakes,  
respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or  
engage with another Website feature.

We collect, process and store your personal data as part of your FashionNova membership. 

**Account Registration**  
  
You may choose to create a personal account on our Website, which may require that you disclose certain personally identifiable information for identification, including a unique email address and demographic information (including, for example, zip code, day and month of your birth and back details).

**Billing and Credit Card Information**  
  
In addition, our services comprise, generally, fashion retail and wholesale services. In order to enable payment by you to fulfill your orders, we may collect name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, and other billing information. This information will only be shared with third parties who facilitate completion of the purchase transaction, such as by fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments.  
  
We will not disclose your billing and/or credit card information with other third parties unless required by law or a court order, or unless disclosure is required to address an issue implicated by the financial transaction. For instance, if you claim that your billing and/or credit card information was used to make a purchase you did not authorize, details about the transaction may be disclosed to law enforcement and any party we deem necessary to address the matter.

**Gift Recipient Information**  
  
We may also collect information about gift recipients, including name, delivery address, phone number, and other information, so that may be may be able to fulfill any purchases made on their behalf. We do not use the information we collect about gift recipients for marketing purposes.  
  
 **Changes to Personally Identifiable Information**  
  
To change any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, please access the “My Account” section of our Webpage. You may also contact us [HERE](https://support.fashionnova.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=167186).  
  
 **How is My Information Used?**  
  
The information we collect is used for a variety of purposes, such as:

  * to enable your use of our Services, such as enabling you to make purchases of clothing and accessories we have listed for sale by processing your transactions;
  * to perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of our Services to improve our relationship with our customers by personalizing your site experience where possible, allowing us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested;
  * to improve our service to you in responding to any of your customer service requests;  
for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base to improve our relationship with our customers;
  * to customize your experience by allowing advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent; and
  * to administer contests, promotions, surveys, and/or other site features.

Without your explicit permission, we only disclose your personal data to third parties in order to fulfill our contractual obligations (for example, the delivery of our products by the carrier and the logistics companies) and for accounting purposes (eg collection companies or banks). These service providers explicitly use your data only for the purpose of the contract.   
  
If the legitimate purpose of the processing of your data is canceled or if the applicable law requires it, your personal data will be deleted accordingly. I authorize FashionNova to collect, process and use my personal data in accordance with this privacy policy.  
  
 **Direct Communication**  
  
We may contact you via email, telephone, text, paper mail, or other delivery methods regarding the status and/or delivery of any products or services that you may have purchased through this Website.  
  
 **E-mail List**  
  
Visitors to the Website who register an account or engage with other site features, such as marketing programs and “members only” content, will be given a choice whether they would like to be included on our email list and receive e-mail newsletters from us.  
  
If you have opted-in to receive email newsletters from us, you may periodically receive communications including links to and information regarding sales, promotions, sweepstakes, and other information that we believe you may find interesting.  
  
If you have not opted-in to receive email newsletters from us, you will not receive these e-mails.  
  
 **How to Opt-Out of E-mail List**  
  
If you would no longer like to receive email newsletters from us, you can unsubscribe by selecting the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of any of our promotional emails.

**How is My Information Stored?**

We implement a variety of security measures in an effort to reasonably maintain the safety of your personal information.  Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.

**What Information is Collected Through Technology and by Third-Parties?**

As you browse through our website and place orders, we automatically collect and store the following non-personal, or anonymous information about your visit:

  * the date and time you access our site;
  * the pages you visit on our site;
  * if You navigate to our site by clicking a link, the location of that link;
  * the technical capabilities of the computer you use to access our site;
  * the internet service provider You use to connect to our site (for example "companyX.com" if you have a commercial internet account, or "universityX.edu" if you connect from a university); and
  * the IP address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the internet) from which you access our site.

We use this information, in the aggregate, to make our website more useful to visitors — to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology used, to detect operational problems, and to improve the website's overall security.

**Cookies, Beacons, Local Storage and Other Similar Technologies**

**Cookies**  
What are cookies?   
Cookies and flash cookies ("cookies") are data that are used in communications networks to store certain information needed when browsing. "Visit Cookies" identify a visit and are deleted after closing the page and "Cookies Permanents" remain permanently in your browsing history on your data carrier.   
  
You can delete the data from the browsing history or stop the of collected data.

 We use "cookies," Web beacons, HTML5 local storage and other similar technologies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For example, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You may choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you may even choose to turn off all cookies through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look to your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Do note, that if you turn cookies off, you may lose access to many features that make your experience on our website more efficient, and some of our services will not function properly. If you turn cookies off and are unable to place an order online through our website, you may still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.

We do not respond to browser-based "do not track" signals. 

We may transmit non-personally identifiable website usage information to third parties in order to show you advertising for Fashion Nova when you visit other sites.

**What kind of cookies do we use?**  
FashionNova uses visiting cookies and permanent cookies. Cookies are necessary for easy and convenient navigation on our website. Visit cookies help us to update your cart according to your wishes during your visit to our website. Persistent cookies help us to display products that you might prefer. The information provided is anonymous without any link to personal data.   
  
**How are cookies used by Third Parties?**  
We also use a third type of cookie on our website to improve our products and services. In particular, we use the following cookies:   
  
We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA ("Google"). Google uses cookies to obtain information about our users' access to our website. The information about your browsing on our website generated by the cookie will normally be transferred to a Google server in the United States where it will be saved. Google will make your IP address anonymous in the EU Member States or other countries belonging to the European Economic Area agreements. Only in exceptional cases will the complete IP address be transferred to the Google server in the United States to be anonymous to other foreign countries. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website and to report on your activity. The IP address of your browser transferred by Google Analytics will not be shared with other Google files. You can refuse the storage of cookies by setting the appropriate adjustments on your browser. In addition, if you wish to prevent the processing of your data (including your IP address) generated by Google cookies, you can download and install the browser plugin: You can refuse the storage of cookies by setting the appropriate adjustments on your browser. In addition, if you wish to prevent the processing of your data (including your IP address) generated by Google cookies, you can download and install the browser plugin: You can refuse the storage of cookies by setting the appropriate adjustments on your browser. In addition, if you wish to prevent the processing of your data (including your IP address) generated by Google cookies, you can download and install the browser plugin:https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en .   
  
We use DoubleClick DART (Dynamic Advertising Reporting and Targeting) - Google Inc. Cookies, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"), to process information about your visits to sites Internet (ours and others) for marketing purposes. Technology provides targeted advertising services over the Internet. You can block the use of DoubleClick cookies.   
  
**How can I prevent the use of cookies?**  
You can prevent the storage of cookies by making appropriate adjustments on your browser. This could, however, result in limiting certain functions of our website.   
If you want to disable the processing of your data (including your IP address) generated by 

Google's cookies, you can download and install the browser plugin: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en . You can also disable the use of DoubleClick 

DART cookies by visiting the Google Privacy Policy page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/opt-out.html  
I give FashionNova and its operating partners ("Third Party") permission to insert cookies. I can withdraw my consent by changing my browser settings to block cookies.  
  
 **Analytics, Log Files and Reading History**  
We gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, operating system and other usage information about the use of our Services, including a history of the pages you view.

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, including customized recommendations, advertising, to improve marketing, and to track access and use of our Services across the devices that you may use to access our Services.

We have hired third parties to provide us information, reports, and analysis about the usage, browsing patterns of our users. They may independently record the type of device and operating system you are using, general location information, as well as events that occur on our Website, such as how often you use our Website. 

**Which Third-party Persons/Entities is My Personally Identifiable Information Shared With?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include www.FashionNova.com. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep your information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 

**Third Parties**

We may share information about our visitors in aggregate or de-identified form with third parties. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to indicate a restriction of our use or sharing of aggregated or de-identified information in any way. 

We may also include links to third party websites on our Website in an attempt to provide you with increased value. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including whether a specific link works). 

**Disclosure by Necessity**

We may occasionally access, preserve, and/or disclose personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * comply with the law or with legal process;
  * protect and defend our rights and property;
  * protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Services; or transfer
  * protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions). 

As we continue to develop our business, we or our affiliates may sell or buy other businesses or entities, or we may merge with another company, or be bought by another company. In such transactions, personal information may be among the transferred assets.

Your information may be stored and processed in any country in which we maintain facilities or conduct operations. By using our Website, your personal information may be transferred outside of your country of use and/or residence.

When your account becomes inactive, your information may remain in our computers, electronic databases, and archives, and may not be reasonably capable of expungement.  

**Miscellaneous**

**Children's Guidelines**

COPPA Compliance. We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13.

**Amendments**

This Privacy Policy may be amended by us at any time and without notice, but only by amending this Policy as posted on this Website. Any amendments will become effective 30 days after being posted on the website unless circumstances require that a change is immediately implemented.

**Using Social Plugins**  
Using Facebook Plugins   
  
We use Social Plugins from the Facebook social network, provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 California Ave., Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA ("Facebook"). The plugins are marked by the Facebook logo or with the addition of "social plug-in of Facebook" or "Facebook Social Plugin". You can preview Facebook Plugins here: http://developers.facebook.com/plugins .   
  
When you open a FashionNova page that includes one of these plugins, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Facebook server. The content of the plugin will be transferred directly to your browser and integrated into the site. Thanks to this integration, Facebook receives information about your visits to our website, even if you do not have a Facebook profile or are not connected to your profile. This information (including your IP address) will be transferred directly to the Facebook server in the United States where it is also registered. If you are connected to Facebook, Facebook can immediately follow your visit to FashionNova with your Facebook profile.  
If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking on the "like" button or comments on something, this information will also be transferred and saved on the Facebook server. The information can also be published on your Facebook profile.   
For more information about the purpose and volume of the data collection, their subsequent processing and use by Facebook or your profile rights and settings regarding privacy policy protection, please check the Facebook Privacy Policy, http://www.facebook.com/policy.php. If you wish to prevent the transfer of your information to your Facebook profile, disconnect from your Facebook profile before visiting our website. You can also prevent Facebook plugins from loading by installing "Facebook Blocker" ( http://webgraph.com/resources/facebookblocker/ ).   
  
**The use of Google + plugins (for example "+1")**   
  
We use Google + social plugins, operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"). Plugins are identifiable for example with the buttons with the sign "+1" on a white background or color. You can find an overview of Google plugins [HERE](https://developers.google.com/+/plugins%20). When you open a page on our website that includes a Google + plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Google server. The content of the plugin will be transferred directly to your browser and integrated into the site. With this integration, Google receives information about your visits to our website, even if you do not have a Google profile or are not connected to your profile. This information (including your IP address) will be directly transferred and saved on the Google server in the United States. If you're signed in to Google, Google can track your visit to FashionNova.com with your Google + profile. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking on the "like" button or comment on something, this information will also be transferred and saved on the Google server. This information will also be published on your Google + profile. For more information about the purpose and volume of the data collection, their subsequent processing and use by Google or your profile rights and settings regarding the protection of the privacy policy, please check the policy Google's privacy policy by clicking [HERE](http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/politique/1button.html). If you want to prevent the transfer of information collected on your Google + profile, sign out of your Google + profile before visiting our website. You can also prevent Google Plugins from loading by installing Script-Blocker "NoScript" ( http://noscript.net/ ).   
  
**The use of Twitter plugins (eg the "Twitter" button)**  
  
FashionNova uses the plugins of the Twitter microblogging service, provided by Twitter Inc., 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA ("Twitter "). The plugins are marked by the Twitter logo, a bluebird. You can see a preview of Twitter plugins [HERE](https://twitter.com/about/resources/buttons).

If you visit a FashionNova page that includes a Twitter plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to the Twitter server. The content of the plugin will be transferred directly to your browser and integrated into the site. With this integration, Twitter receives information about your visits to our website, even if you do not have a Twitter profile or are not connected to your profile. This information (including your IP address) will be directly transferred and saved on the Twitter server in the United States. If you are connected to Twitter, Twitter can follow your visit on FashionNova.fr with your Twitter profile. If you interact with the plugins, for example by clicking on the "like" button or comment on something, this information will also be transferred and saved on the Twitter server. This information will also be posted on your Twitter profile. For more information about the purpose and volume of the data collection, their subsequent processing and use by Twitter or your profile rights and settings regarding the protection of the privacy policy, please check the policy of Twitter's privacy policy by clicking [HERE](https://twitter.com/privacy). If you wish to prevent the transfer of the information collected on your Twitter profile, disconnect from your Twitter profile before visiting FashionNova. You can also prevent Twitter plugins from loading by installing Script-Blocker "NoScript" ( http://noscript.net/ ).

**Data processing outside the EEA**  
Fashion Nova is a company established in the USA. This means that your personal information is transferred and stored outside of the EEA in a jurisdiction that does not offer the same protection for your personal information as the country in which you are located. Personal data will be processed through the network of Shopify servers. We request that our data processing partners outside the EEA comply with the European Union Data Protection Directive 95/46/ EC and to national legislation.

**Information, correction, blocking and deletion of data; Right to retract**  
According to European legislation, you can request the information and data stored in relation to you and the correction, blocking and deletion of these data. You can contact us at any time see below for contact information. 

Address:  
FashionNova  
2801 East 46th Street Vernon  
Email: [info@FashionNova.com](mailto:info@FashionNova.com)

Access our customer inquiry form [HERE](https://support.fashionnova.com/hc/en-us/requests/new).

According to EU law, EU Constituents may also wholly or partially withdraw your data from the collection, processing or use by FashionNova. Please note that in such a case, the functionality of our website will be limited or removed.
